

ABOUT ME

I am a diligent student with an unwavering commitment to delivering quality work for web design. My journey in drawing and design has not only honed my creative skills but also provided a solid foundation for crafting beautiful websites. My experience in the part-time job not only enhanced my effective communication skills but also fostered a heightened sense of responsibility. I always hold myself accountable for my assigned tasks!

SKILLS

- Painting and Design
- Color MixingTeamwork and Collaboration
- Organization and Time Management
- Attention to Detail
- Patient Data Coding
- Website Development
- HTML/JavaScript/CSS

EDUCATION

Musashino Art University - Tokyo, Japan Painting, 07/2019

University of San Francisco - San Francisco, CA Management, 05/2022

UC San Diego - San Diego J.D.

International Business, Expected in 03/2024

EXPERIENCE

STUDENT IN PAINTING COURSE | 10/2018 to 07/2019

Musashino Art University - Tokyo, Japan

- Learned various brushstrokes and how to manipulate brushes to create different textures and effects.
- Understand the basic principles of color theory and color mixing, learning how to mix primary colors to achieve the desired hues.

PART-TIME PACKING DESIGNER | 09/2021 to 07/2022

Hangzhou Credible Sanitary Products Co., Ltd. - Hangzhou, China

- Developed practical design skills, learning how to apply design principles in real work, including color theory, layout, etc.
- Worked with other teammates, improving collaboration and communication skills as well realizing the importance of exchanging feedback in the design process.

STUDENT IN COG3 CLASS | 09/2023 to 12/2023 UC San Diego - San Diego, CA

- Mastered basic skills of web development, including writing HTML code and JavaScript code, using Bootstrap and Figma, etc.
- Enhanced color proficiency, learning color classifications and the relationship between color and moods.